http://www.eurekalog.com/privacy.php

Change Log
We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our company.
Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of the Neos Eureka S.r.l.
The use of the Internet pages of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. is possible without any indication of personal data;
however, if a data subject wants to use special company services via our website, processing of personal data could become necessary.
If the processing of personal data is necessary and there is no statutory basis for such processing, we generally obtain consent from the data subject.
Terms of Service
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
Information Collection and Use
Neos Eureka S.r.l. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Neos Eureka S.r.l. collects information from our users and site visitors at several different points.
Customer Support
In order to receive customer support, you must complete the customer support form.
During this process you are required to give your contact information (such as name and e-mail address).
This information is only used to contact you about the customer support issue.
The contact information is not added to our contact list or mailing list unless specifically requested.
Placing an Order
We use BlueSnap (formerly called Plimus) as our eCommerce payment processor.
We request information from you on our order form.
Here you must provide contact information (like name and billing address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).
This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your order.
If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you.
We save your contact information for our customer records.
However, we do NOT store your financial information.
Financial information may be stored by BlueSnap.
Please, refer to BlueSnap's Terms of Service and Privacy Policy for more information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that reference information about you on our servers.
Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.
We use cookies to provide an enhanced browsing experience on our web site.
If you reject the cookie, you may have trouble accessing some features on our web site.
Log Files
We are using Google Analytics to analyze trends, track page popularity, and gather information for aggregate use.
This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
Please, refer to Google Analytic's Terms of Service and Privacy Policy for more information.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites.
Neos Eureka S.r.l. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Newsletter
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. Contact information is not shared with any third parties.
Anyone can manually subscribe/unsubscribe to our mailing lists by editing his profile options.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time, our site may request information from you for surveys or contests.
Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.
Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age, and income).
We do not collect your personal data unless you explicitly provide it yourself in the input fields of a survey.
Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.
E-mail is also used to check the uniqueness of the survey.
The contact information is not added to any mailing lists.
Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site and our software.
All collected data is used exclusively within our company, we do not share this data with anyone.
All survey data are sent to our server over a secure TLS protocol, where they are encrypted into the database.
Tell-A-Friend
If you use our referral service for telling a friend about our software, we will ask you for the friend’s name and e-mail address.
Neos Eureka S.r.l. will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site and download the software.
We do not add this information to our contact list or mailing list; The recipient must contact Neos Eureka S.r.l. through the link in the e-mail or this web site.
Security
This website makes every reasonable effort to protect your information.
When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
Your connection is secured with TLS (HTTPS).
We do not store your password.
Special Offers
As our customer you may receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.
This is optional, you must explicitly subscribe to our mailing list in the options of your user profile on our web-site.
Correction/Updating/Removal Personal Information
If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your e-mail), you can edit your information yourself or ask us to do it for you.
You may request to delete your personal information at any time.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail.
Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.
We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Privacy Policy
The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number of a data subject shall always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with the country-specific data protection regulations applicable to the Neos Eureka S.r.l.
By means of this data protection declaration, our company would like to inform the general public of the nature, scope, and purpose of the personal data we collect, use and process.
Furthermore, data subjects are informed, by means of this data protection declaration, of the rights to which they are entitled.
As the controller, the Neos Eureka S.r.l. has implemented numerous technical and organizational measures to ensure the most complete protection of personal data processed through this website.
However, Internet-based data transmissions may in principle have security gaps, so absolute protection may not be guaranteed.
For this reason, every data subject is free to transfer personal data to us via alternative means, e.g. by telephone.
1. Definitions
The data protection declaration of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. is based on the terms used by the European legislator for the adoption of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Our data protection declaration should be legible and understandable for the general public, as well as our customers and business partners.
To ensure this, we would like to first explain the terminology used.
In this data protection declaration, we use, inter alia, the following terms:
a)
Personal data
Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (“data subject”).
An identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.
b)
Data subject
Data subject is any identified or identifiable natural person, whose personal data is processed by the controller responsible for the processing.
c)
Processing
Processing is any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.
d)
Restriction of processing
Restriction of processing is the marking of stored personal data with the aim of limiting their processing in the future.
e)
Profiling
Profiling means any form of automated processing of personal data consisting of the use of personal data to evaluate certain personal aspects relating to a natural person, in particular to analyse or predict aspects concerning that natural person's performance at work, economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behaviour, location or movements.
f)
Pseudonymisation
Pseudonymisation is the processing of personal data in such a manner that the personal data can no longer be attributed to a specific data subject without the use of additional information, provided that such additional information is kept separately and is subject to technical and organisational measures to ensure that the personal data are not attributed to an identified or identifiable natural person.
g)
Controller or controller responsible for the processing
Controller or controller responsible for the processing is the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by Union or Member State law, the controller or the specific criteria for its nomination may be provided for by Union or Member State law.
h)
Processor
Processor is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the controller.
i)
Recipient
Recipient is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which the personal data are disclosed, whether a third party or not. However, public authorities which may receive personal data in the framework of a particular inquiry in accordance with Union or Member State law shall not be regarded as recipients; the processing of those data by those public authorities shall be in compliance with the applicable data protection rules according to the purposes of the processing.
j)
Third party
Third party is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data.
k)
Consent
Consent of the data subject is any freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous indication of the data subject's wishes by which he or she, by a statement or by a clear affirmative action, signifies agreement to the processing of personal data relating to him or her.
2. Name and Address of the controller
Controller for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), other data protection laws applicable in Member states of the European Union and other provisions related to data protection is:
Neos Eureka S.r.l.
Via Giotto, 78
90145 Palermo
Italy
VAT ID: IT06282880829
Web-site: www.eurekalog.com
Contact Us
3. Cookies
The Internet pages of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. use cookies.
Cookies are text files that are stored in a computer system via an Internet browser.
Many Internet sites and servers use cookies.
Many cookies contain a so-called cookie ID.
A cookie ID is a unique identifier of the cookie.
It consists of a character string through which Internet pages and servers can be assigned to the specific Internet browser in which the cookie was stored.
This allows visited Internet sites and servers to differentiate the individual browser of the dats subject from other Internet browsers that contain other cookies.
A specific Internet browser can be recognized and identified using the unique cookie ID.
Through the use of cookies, the Neos Eureka S.r.l. can provide the users of this website with more user-friendly services that would not be possible without the cookie setting.
By means of a cookie, the information and offers on our website can be optimized with the user in mind.
Cookies allow us, as previously mentioned, to recognize our website users.
The purpose of this recognition is to make it easier for users to utilize our website.
The website user that uses cookies, e.g. does not have to enter access data each time the website is accessed, because this is taken over by the website, and the cookie is thus stored on the user's computer system.
Another example is the cookie of a shopping cart in an online shop.
The online store remembers the articles that a customer has placed in the virtual shopping cart via a cookie.
The data subject may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies through our website by means of a corresponding setting of the Internet browser used, and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies.
Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs.
This is possible in all popular Internet browsers.
If the data subject deactivates the setting of cookies in the Internet browser used, not all functions of our website may be entirely usable.
4. Collection of general data and information
The website of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. collects a series of general data and information when a data subject or automated system calls up the website.
This general data and information are stored in the server log files.
Collected may be:
the browser types and versions used,
the operating system used by the accessing system,
the website from which an accessing system reaches our website (so-called referrers),
the sub-websites,
the date and time of access to the Internet site,
an Internet protocol address (IP address),
the Internet service provider of the accessing system,
any other similar data and information that may be used in the event of attacks on our information technology systems.
When using these general data and information, the Neos Eureka S.r.l. does not draw any conclusions about the data subject.
Rather, this information is needed to:
deliver the content of our website correctly,
optimize the content of our website as well as its advertisement,
ensure the long-term viability of our information technology systems and website technology,
provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution in case of a cyber-attack.
Therefore, the Neos Eureka S.r.l. analyzes anonymously collected data and information statistically, with the aim of increasing the data protection and data security of our company, and to ensure an optimal level of protection for the personal data we process.
The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately from all personal data provided by a data subject.
5. Contact possibility via the website
The website of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. contains information that enables a quick electronic contact to our company, as well as direct communication with us, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address).
If a data subject contacts the controller by e-mail or via a contact form, the personal data transmitted by the data subject are automatically stored.
Such personal data transmitted on a voluntary basis by a data subject to the data controller are stored for the purpose of processing or contacting the data subject.
There is no transfer of this personal data to third parties.
6. Routine erasure and blocking of personal data
The data controller shall process and store the personal data of the data subject only for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of storage, or as far as this is granted by the European legislator or other legislators in laws or regulations to which the controller is subject to.
If the storage purpose is not applicable, or if a storage period prescribed by the European legislator or another competent legislator expires, the personal data are routinely blocked or erased in accordance with legal requirements.
7. Rights of the data subject
a) Right of confirmation
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller the confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning him or her are being processed.
If a data subject wishes to avail himself of this right of confirmation, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.
b) Right of access
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller free information about his or her personal data stored at any time and a copy of this information.
Furthermore, the European directives and regulations grant the data subject access to the following information:
the purposes of the processing;
the categories of personal data concerned;
the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations;
where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored, or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;
the existence of the right to request from the controller rectification or erasure of personal data, or restriction of processing of personal data concerning the data subject, or to object to such processing;
the existence of the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;
where the personal data are not collected from the data subject, any available information as to their source;
the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred to in Article 22(1) and (4) of the GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and envisaged consequences of such processing for the data subject.
Furthermore, the data subject shall have a right to obtain information as to whether personal data are transferred to a third country or to an international organisation.
Where this is the case, the data subject shall have the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards relating to the transfer.
If a data subject wishes to avail himself of this right of access, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.
c) Right to rectification
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller without undue delay the rectification of inaccurate personal data concerning him or her.
Taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject shall have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.
If a data subject wishes to exercise this right to rectification, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.
d) Right to erasure (Right to be forgotten)
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller the erasure of personal data concerning him or her without undue delay, and the controller shall have the obligation to erase personal data without undue delay where one of the following grounds applies, as long as the processing is not necessary:
The personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed.
The data subject withdraws consent to which the processing is based according to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, and where there is no other legal ground for the processing.
The data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or the data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(2) of the GDPR.
The personal data have been unlawfully processed.
The personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject.
The personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services referred to in Article 8(1) of the GDPR.
If one of the aforementioned reasons applies, and a data subject wishes to request the erasure of personal data stored by the Neos Eureka S.r.l., he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the controller.
An employee of Neos Eureka S.r.l. shall promptly ensure that the erasure request is complied with immediately.
Where the controller has made personal data public and is obliged pursuant to Article 17(1) to erase the personal data, the controller, taking account of available technology and the cost of implementation, shall take reasonable steps, including technical measures, to inform other controllers processing the personal data that the data subject has requested erasure by such controllers of any links to, or copy or replication of, those personal data, as far as processing is not required.
An employees of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. will arrange the necessary measures in individual cases.
e) Right of restriction of processing
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to obtain from the controller restriction of processing where one of the following applies:
The accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject, for a period enabling the controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data.
The processing is unlawful and the data subject opposes the erasure of the personal data and requests instead the restriction of their use instead.
The controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the processing, but they are required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
The data subject has objected to processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of the controller override those of the data subject.
If one of the aforementioned conditions is met, and a data subject wishes to request the restriction of the processing of personal data stored by the Neos Eureka S.r.l., he or she may at any time contact any employee of the controller.
The employee of the Neos Eureka S.r.l. will arrange the restriction of the processing.
f) Right to data portability
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator, to receive the personal data concerning him or her, which was provided to a controller, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.
He or she shall have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the controller to which the personal data have been provided, as long as the processing is based on consent pursuant to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, or on a contract pursuant to point (b) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, and the processing is carried out by automated means, as long as the processing is not necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller.
Furthermore, in exercising his or her right to data portability pursuant to Article 20(1) of the GDPR, the data subject shall have the right to have personal data transmitted directly from one controller to another, where technically feasible and when doing so does not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.
In order to assert the right to data portability, the data subject may at any time contact any employee of the Neos Eureka S.r.l.
g) Right to object
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to object, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, at any time, to processing of personal data concerning him or her, which is based on point (e) or (f) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR. This also applies to profiling based on these provisions.
The Neos Eureka S.r.l. shall no longer process the personal data in the event of the objection, unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject, or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.
If the Neos Eureka S.r.l. processes personal data for direct marketing purposes, the data subject shall have the right to object at any time to processing of personal data concerning him or her for such marketing.
This applies to profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing.
If the data subject objects to the Neos Eureka S.r.l. to the processing for direct marketing purposes, the Neos Eureka S.r.l. will no longer process the personal data for these purposes.
In addition, the data subject has the right, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, to object to processing of personal data concerning him or her by the Neos Eureka S.r.l. for scientific or historical research purposes, or for statistical purposes pursuant to Article 89(1) of the GDPR, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.
In order to exercise the right to object, the data subject may contact any employee of the Neos Eureka S.r.l.
In addition, the data subject is free in the context of the use of information society services, and notwithstanding Directive 2002/58/EC, to use his or her right to object by automated means using technical specifications.
h) Automated individual decision-making, including profiling
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning him or her, or similarly significantly affects him or her, as long as the decision (1) is not is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller, or (2) is not authorised by Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject and which also lays down suitable measures to safeguard the data subject's rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, or (3) is not based on the data subject's explicit consent.
If the decision (1) is necessary for entering into, or the performance of, a contract between the data subject and a data controller, or (2) it is based on the data subject's explicit consent, the Neos Eureka S.r.l. shall implement suitable measures to safeguard the data subject's rights and freedoms and legitimate interests, at least the right to obtain human intervention on the part of the controller, to express his or her point of view and contest the decision.
If the data subject wishes to exercise the rights concerning automated individual decision-making, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the Neos Eureka S.r.l.
i) Right to withdraw data protection consent
Each data subject shall have the right granted by the European legislator to withdraw his or her consent to processing of his or her personal data at any time.
If the data subject wishes to exercise the right to withdraw the consent, he or she may, at any time, contact any employee of the Neos Eureka S.r.l.
8. Data protection provisions about the application and use of Google Analytics (with anonymization function)
On this website, the controller has integrated the component of Google Analytics (with the anonymizer function).
Google Analytics is a web analytics service.
Web analytics is the collection, gathering, and analysis of data about the behavior of visitors to websites.
A web analysis service collects, inter alia, data about the website from which a person has come (the so-called referrer), which sub-pages were visited, or how often and for what duration a sub-page was viewed.
Web analytics are mainly used for the optimization of a website.
The operator of the Google Analytics component is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States.
For the web analytics through Google Analytics the controller uses the application "_gat. _anonymizeIp".
By means of this application the IP address of the Internet connection of the data subject is abridged by Google and anonymised when accessing our websites from a Member State of the European Union or another Contracting State to the Agreement on the European Economic Area.
The purpose of the Google Analytics component is to analyze the traffic on our website.
Google uses the collected data and information, inter alia, to evaluate the use of our website and to provide online reports, which show the activities on our websites, and to provide other services concerning the use of our Internet site for us.
Google Analytics places a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject.
The definition of cookies is explained above.
With the setting of the cookie, Google is enabled to analyze the use of our website.
With each call-up to one of the individual pages of this Internet site, which is operated by the controller and into which a Google Analytics component was integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the data subject will automatically submit data through the Google Analytics component.
During the course of this technical procedure, the company Google gains knowledge of personal information, such as the IP address of the data subject, which serves Google, inter alia, to understand the origin of visitors and clicks.
The cookie is used to store personal information, such as the access time, the location from which the access was made, and the frequency of visits of our website by the data subject.
With each visit to our Internet site, such personal data, including the IP address of the Internet access used by the data subject, will be transmitted to Google in the United States of America.
These personal data are stored by Google in the United States of America.
Google may pass these personal data collected through the technical procedure to third parties.
The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the web browser used and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies.
Such an adjustment to the Internet browser used would also prevent Google Analytics from setting a cookie on the information technology system of the data subject.
In addition, cookies already in use by Google Analytics may be deleted at any time via a web browser or other software programs.
In addition, the data subject has the possibility of objecting to a collection of data that are generated by Google Analytics, which is related to the use of this website, as well as the processing of this data by Google and the chance to preclude any such. For this purpose, the data subject must download a browser add-on under the link https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and install it. This browser add-on tells Google Analytics through a JavaScript, that any data and information about the visits of Internet pages may not be transmitted to Google Analytics. The installation of the browser add-ons is considered an objection by Google. If the information technology system of the data subject is later deleted, formatted, or newly installed, then the data subject must reinstall the browser add-ons to disable Google Analytics. If the browser add-on was uninstalled by the data subject or any other person who is attributable to their sphere of competence, or is disabled, it is possible to execute the reinstallation or reactivation of the browser add-ons.
Further information and the applicable data protection provisions of Google may be retrieved here and here.
Google Analytics is further explained under the following link.
9. Payment Method: Data protection provisions about the use of BlueSnap as a payment processor
On this website, the controller has integrated components of BlueSnap.
BlueSnap is an online payment service provider.
BlueSnap is able to process virtual payments through many different payments type (as credit cards, PayPal, Purchase Order, Bank transfer and more).
The BlueSnap Corporate Headquarters Office is at:
800 South Street, Suite 640
Waltham, MA 02453
All the payments are managed directly from the BlueSnap website, after any successful payment BlueSnap send the new order data to our server to allow we to create a new customer and process the new order.
The personal data transmitted to our server is usually first name, last name, address, e-mail address, IP address, telephone number, mobile phone number, or other data necessary for payment processing.
The processing of the purchase contract also requires such personal data, which are in connection with the respective order.
The transmission of the data is aimed at payment processing and fraud prevention.
BlueSnap will, if necessary, pass on personal data to affiliates and service providers or subcontractors (as PayPal) to the extent that this is necessary to fulfill contractual obligations or for data to be processed in the order.
The data subject has the possibility to revoke consent for the handling of personal data at any time from BlueSnap.
A revocation shall not have any effect on personal data which must be processed, used or transmitted in accordance with (contractual) payment processing.
The applicable data protection provisions of BlueSnap may be retrieved here.
10. Legal basis for the processing
Art. 6(1) lit. a GDPR serves as the legal basis for processing operations for which we obtain consent for a specific processing purpose.
If the processing of personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is party, as is the case, for example, when processing operations are necessary for the supply of goods or to provide any other service, the processing is based on Article 6(1) lit. b GDPR.
The same applies to such processing operations which are necessary for carrying out pre-contractual measures, for example in the case of inquiries concerning our products or services.
Our company is subject to a legal obligation by which processing of personal data is required, such as for the fulfillment of tax obligations, the processing is based on Art. 6(1) lit. c GDPR.
In rare cases, the processing of personal data may be necessary to protect the vital interests of the data subject or of another natural person.
This would be the case, for example, if a visitor were injured in our company and his name, age, health insurance data or other vital information would have to be passed on to a doctor, hospital or other third party.
Then the processing would be based on Art. 6(1) lit. d GDPR.
Finally, processing operations could be based on Article 6(1) lit. f GDPR.
This legal basis is used for processing operations which are not covered by any of the abovementioned legal grounds, if processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by our company or by a third party, except where such interests are overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection of personal data.
Such processing operations are particularly permissible because they have been specifically mentioned by the European legislator.
He considered that a legitimate interest could be assumed if the data subject is a client of the controller (Recital 47 Sentence 2 GDPR).
11. The legitimate interests pursued by the controller or by a third party
Where the processing of personal data is based on Article 6(1) lit. f GDPR our legitimate interest is to carry out our business in favor of the well-being of all our employees and the shareholders.
12. Period for which the personal data will be stored
The criteria used to determine the period of storage of personal data is the respective statutory retention period.
After expiration of that period, the corresponding data is routinely deleted, as long as it is no longer necessary for the fulfillment of the contract or the initiation of a contract.
13. Provision of personal data as statutory or contractual requirement; Requirement necessary to enter into a contract; Obligation of the data subject to provide the personal data; possible consequences of failure to provide such data
We clarify that the provision of personal data is partly required by law (e.g. tax regulations) or can also result from contractual provisions (e.g. information on the contractual partner).
Sometimes it may be necessary to conclude a contract that the data subject provides us with personal data, which must subsequently be processed by us.
The data subject is, for example, obliged to provide us with personal data when our company signs a contract with him or her.
The non-provision of the personal data would have the consequence that the contract with the data subject could not be concluded.
Before personal data is provided by the data subject, the data subject must contact any employee.
The employee clarifies to the data subject whether the provision of the personal data is required by law or contract or is necessary for the conclusion of the contract, whether there is an obligation to provide the personal data and the consequences of non-provision of the personal data.
14. Existence of automated decision-making
As a responsible company, we do not use automatic decision-making or profiling.
About Us - Privacy Policy - Contacts
Copyright
©
Neos Eureka S.r.l. - VAT ID: IT06282880829
